emailsignaturerescue.com 2019-05-14

# Email Signature Rescue Privacy Policy

Div Party Pty Ltd ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://emailsignaturerescue.com and https://esig.ly website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our [Terms and Conditions](https://emailsignaturerescue.com/about/terms) and our [Security and Data Policy](https://emailsignaturerescue.com/about/security-data-policy).

 **Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and/or your users. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, email addresses, names, phone numbers, addresses, other information ("Personal Information").

The purpose for which we collect personal information is to provide you with the best service experience possible on the Service and for our internal business purposes that form part of normal business practices. Some provision of personal information is optional. However, if you do not provide us with certain types of personal information, you may be unable to enjoy the full functionality of the Service.

 **Log Data**

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

**Cookies**

What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

How do we use cookies?

Brochure Site - https://emailsignaturerescue.com

We use cookies on our Brochure Site, to remember user choices and actions. An example is when you accept the cookie policy notification, a cookie is stored to remember that you have accepted the policy and this now longer needs to be shown. Other services that we have installed on our Brochure Site through javascript snippets also use cookies. Some examples of services we have installed include Google Analytics, LeadDyno and FullStory. You can learn more about their own cookie policies at their respective websites.

App Site - https://esig.ly

We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

We send a session cookie to your computer when you log in to your User account. This type of cookie helps if you visit multiple pages on the Service during the same session, so that you don't need to enter your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires.

We also use longer-lasting cookies for other purposes such as to display your Content and account information. We encode our cookie so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. Users always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. If you disable cookies on your browser, please note that some parts of our Service may not function as effectively or may be considerably slower.

How to control cookies

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.

Accepting or Declining Cookies

On our brochure site, you will see a notice at the bottom with the heading "Your Privacy Is Important". If the notice is closed, open the notice by clicking on the heading. Under the heading, you will see options to Allow Cookies, Decline Cookies and allow partial cookies depending on your own personal preferences.

The cookie categories include;

  * **Necessary Cookies:** Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
  * **Anonymous Cookies:** Anonymous cookies include cookies used for Google Analytics and FullStory which are software programs we use to track pages visited and user actions on our site to improve our services. IP addresses are anonymous, no personal data is collected.
  * **Affiliate Cookies** : Affiliate Cookies are used to track visitors across websites. Affiliate Cookies collect and log IP addresses in our Affiliate software, LeadDyno. They are only matched to user's email address if that user has clicked on an Affiliate Referral Link to visit our website and chooses to sign up to our service within 60 days of clicking on that link. The personal data collected is only used to match the Affiliate Referral to the user sign up so we can make commission payments to our Affiliates.

**Behavioral Remarketing**

Div Party Pty Ltd uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

  * Google

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

  * Twitter

Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.

You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://twitter.com/privacy

  * Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217

Facebook adheres the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation

  * Pinterest

Pinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc.

You can opt-out from Pinterest's interest-based ads by enabling the "Do Not Track" functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions: http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy

  * AdRoll

AdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.

You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page: http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false

For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page: http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

 **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

 **Compliance With Laws**

We may disclose personal information in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

 **Security**

Please see our [Security and Data Policy](https://emailsignaturerescue.com/security-data-policy).

 **International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Australia and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to Australia and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

 **Access and Correction**

Australian Privacy Principle 6 of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) allows you to get access to, and correct, the personal information we hold about you in certain circumstances. If you would like to obtain such access, please contact us on the details set out above.

Please note that the access and correction requirements under this Privacy Policy operates alongside and do not replace other informal or legal procedures by which an individual can be provided access to, or correction of, their personal information, including the requirements under the Freedom of Information Act 1982 (Cth).

 **Complaints**

Australian Privacy Principle 1 of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) allows you to make a complaint about any alleged breaches of privacy. In order to lodge a complaint with us, please contact us using the details above with the following information:

  * Your name and address;
  * Details of the alleged breach of privacy; and
  * URL link to the alleged breach of privacy (if applicable).

Please allow us 30 days to investigate your complaint, after which we will contact you immediately to resolve the issue.

 **Retention of Information**

We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. This includes when you cancel your account with us. If you want us to delete all held data, please contact us and we will do so. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information. You must keep your own, separate back-up records.

 **Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

 **Children's Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from children under 18 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers or replace it with the Personal Information of the Children’s parent or guardian.

 **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

 **Consent**

You warrant that you are able to give consents under Australian Law or, in the event that you do not have the capacity to give consent, you warrant that your guardian or attorney is able to give any consent required under this Privacy Policy on your behalf.

You hereby expressly and voluntarily grant your informed consent to us to deal with your personal information in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Should you retract your consent, you should cancel your account immediately. If you retract your consent, you acknowledge and agree that failure to provide certain types of personal information may not give you access to the full functionality of the Service.

 **Browser Extension**

We do not have full control over the email account of the user, we just receive access to the email client that the user is using to compose their email for the sole purpose of adding in their HTML email signature. The email client controls the events that create and edit the email. When one of these events is occurring, our extension inserts their HTML email signature in a particular position, the users text in the email is not being analyzed or collected and is not being transferred to us in any way. Our browser extension just locates the correct tag in order to correctly insert the HTML email signature in the correct position when composing, replying or forwarding their email.

Our API is used to connect our browser extension with the HTML email signature website app esig.ly. The browser extension sends a request to our system with the unique key that the user is asked to insert, the user obtains this key by securely logging into our website app with their authorised account. The system checks if the request is correct, it then identifies the signature in the system by the corresponding key and inserts the signature into the browser extension. The signature key is unique to that specific signature only ensuring the correct details are pulled into the browser extension. Again, no email letter text is being analyzed or transferred anywhere during this key transmission.

 **General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

For more information on the GDPR, please visit our dedicated page by [clicking here](https://emailsignaturerescue.com/about/general-data-protection-regulation)

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
